{
    "id": "d404340ac3664dffb38a2cfe3c7cc227",
    "title": "Change into plural",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e5aa4204f78c4b44986b0f47890f947d",
            "title": "Singular And Plural",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Can you solve ................................. problems?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "these",
                        "this"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like to buy those .................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "shirt",
                        "shirts"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have not been to .................................. places.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "those"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................... mangoes were very sweet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "That",
                        "Those"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will buy .............................. shirts.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "those"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Look at those ...................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "painting",
                        "paintings"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who planted ................................ trees?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "those"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can take ................................... books.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "those"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have to clean ................................. windows.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "those"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. dresses have shrunk.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "This",
                        "These"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}